<?xml version="1.0" standalone="yes"?>
<rss xmlns:sparkle="http://www.andymatuschak.org/xml-namespaces/sparkle" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>Clawdbot</title>
        <item>
            <title>2026.1.10</title>
            <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jan 2026 10:26:34 +0000</pubDate>
            <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/clawdbot/clawdbot/main/appcast.xml</link>
            <sparkle:version>4946</sparkle:version>
            <sparkle:shortVersionString>2026.1.10</sparkle:shortVersionString>
            <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>15.0</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
            <description><![CDATA[<h2>Clawdbot 2026.1.10</h2>
<h3>Highlights</h3>
<ul>
<li>CLI: <code>clawdbot status</code> now table-based + shows OS/update/gateway/daemon/agents/sessions; <code>status --all</code> adds a full read-only debug report (tables, log tails, Tailscale summary, and scan progress via OSC-9 + spinner).</li>
<li>CLI Backends: add Codex CLI fallback with resume support (text output) and JSONL parsing for new runs, plus a live CLI resume probe.</li>
<li>CLI: add <code>clawdbot update</code> (safe-ish git checkout update) + <code>--update</code> shorthand. (#673) — thanks @fm1randa.</li>
<li>Gateway: add OpenAI-compatible <code>/v1/chat/completions</code> HTTP endpoint (auth, SSE streaming, per-agent routing). (#680) — thanks @steipete.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Changes</h3>
<ul>
<li>Onboarding/Models: add first-class Z.AI (GLM) auth choice (<code>zai-api-key</code>) + <code>--zai-api-key</code> flag.</li>
<li>CLI/Onboarding: add OpenRouter API key auth option in configure/onboard. (#703) — thanks @mteam88.</li>
<li>Agents: add human-delay pacing between block replies (modes: off/natural/custom, per-agent configurable). (#446) — thanks @tony-freedomology.</li>
<li>Agents/Browser: add <code>browser.target</code> (sandbox/host/custom) with sandbox host-control gating via <code>agents.defaults.sandbox.browser.allowHostControl</code>, allowlists for custom control URLs/hosts/ports, and expand browser tool docs (remote control, profiles, internals).</li>
<li>Onboarding/Models: add catalog-backed default model picker to onboarding + configure. (#611) — thanks @jonasjancarik.</li>
<li>Agents/OpenCode Zen: update fallback models + defaults, keep legacy alias mappings. (#669) — thanks @magimetal.</li>
<li>Providers: unify group history context wrappers across providers with per-provider/per-account <code>historyLimit</code> overrides (fallback to <code>messages.groupChat.historyLimit</code>). Set <code>0</code> to disable. (#672) — thanks @steipete.</li>
<li>Gateway/Heartbeat: optionally deliver heartbeat <code>Reasoning:</code> output (<code>agents.defaults.heartbeat.includeReasoning</code>). (#690)</li>
<li>Docker: allow optional home volume + extra bind mounts in <code>docker-setup.sh</code>. (#679) — thanks @gabriel-trigo.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Fixes</h3>
<ul>
<li>CLI/Status: expand tables to full terminal width; clarify provider setup vs runtime warnings; richer per-provider detail; token previews in <code>status</code> while keeping <code>status --all</code> redacted; add troubleshooting link footer; keep log tails pasteable; show gateway auth used when reachable; surface provider runtime errors (Signal/iMessage/Slack); harden <code>tailscale status --json</code> parsing; make <code>status --all</code> scan progress determinate; and replace the footer with a 3-line “Next steps” recommendation (share/debug/probe).</li>
<li>CLI/Gateway: clarify that <code>clawdbot gateway status</code> reports RPC health (connect + RPC) and shows RPC failures separately from connect failures.</li>
<li>CLI/Update: gate progress spinner on stdout TTY and align clean-check step label. (#701) — thanks @bjesuiter.</li>
<li>Telegram: add <code>/whoami</code> + <code>/id</code> commands to reveal sender id for allowlists; allow <code>@username</code> and prefixed ids in <code>allowFrom</code> prompts (with stability warning).</li>
<li>Control UI: stop auto-writing <code>telegram.groups["*"]</code> and warn/confirm before enabling wildcard groups.</li>
<li>WhatsApp: send ack reactions only for handled messages and ignore legacy <code>messages.ackReaction</code> (doctor copies to <code>whatsapp.ackReaction</code>). (#629) — thanks @pasogott.</li>
<li>Sandbox/Skills: mirror skills into sandbox workspaces for read-only mounts so SKILL.md stays accessible.</li>
<li>Terminal/Table: ANSI-safe wrapping to prevent table clipping/color loss; add regression coverage.</li>
<li>Docker: allow optional apt packages during image build and document the build arg. (#697) — thanks @gabriel-trigo.</li>
<li>Gateway/Heartbeat: deliver reasoning even when the main heartbeat reply is <code>HEARTBEAT_OK</code>. (#694) — thanks @antons.</li>
<li>macOS: clear unsigned launchd overrides on signed restarts and warn via doctor when attach-only/disable markers are set. (#695) — thanks @jeffersonwarrior.</li>
<li>Agents: enforce single-writer session locks and drop orphan tool results to prevent tool-call ID failures (MiniMax/Anthropic-compatible APIs).</li>
<li>Docs: make <code>clawdbot status</code> the first diagnostic step, clarify <code>status --deep</code> behavior, and document <code>/whoami</code> + <code>/id</code>.</li>
<li>Docs/Testing: clarify live tool+image probes and how to list your testable <code>provider/model</code> ids.</li>
<li>Tests/Live: make gateway bash+read probes resilient to provider formatting while still validating real tool calls.</li>
<li>WhatsApp: detect @lid mentions in groups using authDir reverse mapping + resolve self JID E.164 for mention gating. (#692) — thanks @peschee.</li>
<li>Gateway/Auth: default to token auth on loopback during onboarding, add doctor token generation flow, and tighten audio transcription config to Whisper-only.</li>
<li>Providers: dedupe inbound messages across providers to avoid duplicate LLM runs on redeliveries/reconnects. (#689) — thanks @adam91holt.</li>
<li>Agents: strip <code><thought></code>/<code><antthinking></code> tags from hidden reasoning output and cover tag variants in tests. (#688) — thanks @theglove44.</li>
<li>macOS: save model picker selections as normalized provider/model IDs and keep manual entries aligned. (#683) — thanks @benithors.</li>
<li>Agents: recognize "usage limit" errors as rate limits for failover. (#687) — thanks @evalexpr.</li>
<li>CLI: avoid success message when daemon restart is skipped. (#685) — thanks @carlulsoe.</li>
<li>Commands: disable <code>/config</code> + <code>/debug</code> by default; gate via <code>commands.config</code>/<code>commands.debug</code> and hide from native registration/help output.</li>
<li>Agents/System: clarify that sub-agents remain sandboxed and cannot use elevated host access.</li>
<li>Gateway: disable the OpenAI-compatible <code>/v1/chat/completions</code> endpoint by default; enable via <code>gateway.http.endpoints.chatCompletions.enabled=true</code>.</li>
<li>macOS: stabilize bridge tunnels, guard invoke senders on disconnect, and drain stdout/stderr to avoid deadlocks. (#676) — thanks @ngutman.</li>
<li>Agents/System: clarify sandboxed runtime in system prompt and surface elevated availability when sandboxed.</li>
<li>Auto-reply: prefer <code>RawBody</code> for command/directive parsing (WhatsApp + Discord) and prevent fallback runs from clobbering concurrent session updates. (#643) — thanks @mcinteerj.</li>
<li>WhatsApp: fix group reactions by preserving message IDs and sender JIDs in history; normalize participant phone numbers to JIDs in outbound reactions. (#640) — thanks @mcinteerj.</li>
<li>WhatsApp: expose group participant IDs to the model so reactions can target the right sender.</li>
<li>Cron: <code>wakeMode: "now"</code> waits for heartbeat completion (and retries when the main lane is busy). (#666) — thanks @roshanasingh4.</li>
<li>Agents/OpenAI: fix Responses tool-only → follow-up turn handling (avoid standalone <code>reasoning</code> items that trigger 400 “required following item”) and replay reasoning items in Responses/Codex Responses history for tool-call-only turns.</li>
<li>Sandbox: add <code>clawdbot sandbox explain</code> (effective policy inspector + fix-it keys); improve “sandbox jail” tool-policy/elevated errors with actionable config key paths; link to docs.</li>
<li>Hooks/Gmail: keep Tailscale serve path at <code>/</code> while preserving the public path. (#668) — thanks @antons.</li>
<li>Hooks/Gmail: allow Tailscale target URLs to preserve internal serve paths.</li>
<li>Auth: update Claude Code keychain credentials in-place during refresh sync; share JSON file helpers; add CLI fallback coverage.</li>
<li>Auth: throttle external CLI credential syncs (Claude/Codex), reduce Keychain reads, and skip sync when cached credentials are still fresh.</li>
<li>CLI: respect <code>CLAWDBOT_STATE_DIR</code> for node pairing + voice wake settings storage. (#664) — thanks @azade-c.</li>
<li>Onboarding/Gateway: persist non-interactive gateway token auth in config; add WS wizard + gateway tool-calling regression coverage.</li>
<li>Gateway/Control UI: make <code>chat.send</code> non-blocking, wire Stop to <code>chat.abort</code>, and treat <code>/stop</code> as an out-of-band abort. (#653)</li>
<li>Gateway/Control UI: allow <code>chat.abort</code> without <code>runId</code> (abort active runs), suppress post-abort chat streaming, and prune stuck chat runs. (#653)</li>
<li>Gateway/Control UI: sniff image attachments for chat.send, drop non-images, and log mismatches. (#670) — thanks @cristip73.</li>
<li>macOS: force <code>restart-mac.sh --sign</code> to require identities and keep bundled Node signed for relay verification. (#580) — thanks @jeffersonwarrior.</li>
<li>Gateway/Agent: accept image attachments on <code>agent</code> (multimodal message) and add live gateway image probe (<code>CLAWDBOT_LIVE_GATEWAY_IMAGE_PROBE=1</code>).</li>
<li>CLI: <code>clawdbot sessions</code> now includes <code>elev:*</code> + <code>usage:*</code> flags in the table output.</li>
<li>CLI/Pairing: accept positional provider for <code>pairing list|approve</code> (npm-run compatible); update docs/bot hints.</li>
<li>Branding: normalize user-facing “ClawdBot”/“CLAWDBOT” → “Clawdbot” (CLI, status, docs).</li>
<li>Auto-reply: fix native <code>/model</code> not updating the actual chat session (Telegram/Slack/Discord). (#646)</li>
<li>Doctor: offer to run <code>clawdbot update</code> first on git installs (keeps doctor output aligned with latest).</li>
<li>Doctor: avoid false legacy workspace warning when install dir is <code>~/clawdbot</code>. (#660)</li>
<li>iMessage: fix reasoning persistence across DMs; avoid partial/duplicate replies when reasoning is enabled. (#655) — thanks @antons.</li>
<li>Models/Auth: allow MiniMax API configs without <code>models.providers.minimax.apiKey</code> (auth profiles / <code>MINIMAX_API_KEY</code>). (#656) — thanks @mneves75.</li>
<li>Agents: avoid duplicate replies when the message tool sends. (#659) — thanks @mickahouan.</li>
<li>Agents: harden Cloud Code Assist tool ID sanitization (toolUse/toolCall/toolResult) and scrub extra JSON Schema constraints. (#665) — thanks @sebslight.</li>
<li>Agents: sanitize tool results + Cloud Code Assist tool IDs at context-build time (prevents mid-run strict-provider request rejects).</li>
<li>Agents/Tools: resolve workspace-relative Read/Write/Edit paths; align bash default cwd. (#642) — thanks @mukhtharcm.</li>
<li>Discord: include forwarded message snapshots in agent session context. (#667) — thanks @rubyrunsstuff.</li>
<li>Telegram: add <code>telegram.draftChunk</code> to tune draft streaming chunking for <code>streamMode: "block"</code>. (#667) — thanks @rubyrunsstuff.</li>
<li>Tests/Agents: add regression coverage for workspace tool path resolution and bash cwd defaults.</li>
<li>iOS/Android: enable stricter concurrency/lint checks; fix Swift 6 strict concurrency issues + Android lint errors (ExifInterface, obsolete SDK check). (#662) — thanks @KristijanJovanovski.</li>
<li>iOS/macOS: share <code>AsyncTimeout</code>, require explicit <code>bridgeStableID</code> on connect, and harden tool display defaults (avoids missing-resource label fallbacks).</li>
<li>Telegram: serialize media-group processing to avoid missed albums under load.</li>
<li>Signal: handle <code>dataMessage.reaction</code> events (signal-cli SSE) to avoid broken attachment errors. (#637) — thanks @neist.</li>
<li>Docs: showcase entries for ParentPay, R2 Upload, iOS TestFlight, and Oura Health. (#650) — thanks @henrino3.</li>
<li>Agents: repair session transcripts by dropping duplicate tool results across the whole history (unblocks Anthropic-compatible APIs after retries).</li>
<li>Tests/Live: reset the gateway session between model runs to avoid cross-provider transcript incompatibilities (notably OpenAI Responses reasoning replay rules).</li>
</ul>
<p><a href="https://github.com/clawdbot/clawdbot/blob/main/CHANGELOG.md">View full changelog</a></p>
]]></description>
            <enclosure url="https://github.com/clawdbot/clawdbot/releases/download/v2026.1.10/Clawdbot-2026.1.10.zip" length="199586798" type="application/octet-stream" sparkle:edSignature="Ntb22WL4b0Hu3Ntqm1iqnD+5bUqqa36iSQ8vbT/50C5FnL5IjF4GoHWrfanJ58JhBCQ4eKdK+K0U4OBZiSzZBw=="/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>2026.1.9</title>
            <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jan 2026 05:23:02 +0100</pubDate>
            <link>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/clawdbot/clawdbot/main/appcast.xml</link>
            <sparkle:version>4607</sparkle:version>
            <sparkle:shortVersionString>2026.1.9</sparkle:shortVersionString>
            <sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>15.0</sparkle:minimumSystemVersion>
            <description><![CDATA[<h2>Clawdbot 2026.1.9</h2>
<h3>Highlights</h3>
<ul>
<li>Microsoft Teams provider: polling, attachments, outbound CLI send, per-channel policy.</li>
<li>Models/Auth expansion: OpenCode Zen + MiniMax API onboarding; token auth profiles + auth order; OAuth health in doctor/status.</li>
<li>CLI/Gateway UX: message subcommands, gateway discover/status/SSH, /config + /debug, sandbox CLI.</li>
<li>Provider reliability sweep: WhatsApp contact cards/targets, Telegram audio-as-voice + streaming, Signal reactions, Slack threading, Discord stability.</li>
<li>Auto-reply + status: block-streaming controls, reasoning handling, usage/cost reporting.</li>
<li>Control UI/TUI: queued messages, session links, reasoning view, mobile polish, logs UX.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Breaking</h3>
<ul>
<li>CLI: <code>clawdbot message</code> now subcommands (<code>message send|poll|...</code>) and requires <code>--provider</code> unless only one provider configured.</li>
<li>Commands/Tools: <code>/restart</code> and gateway restart tool disabled by default; enable with <code>commands.restart=true</code>.</li>
</ul>
<h3>New Features and Changes</h3>
<ul>
<li>Models/Auth: OpenCode Zen onboarding (#623) — thanks @magimetal; MiniMax Anthropic-compatible API + hosted onboarding (#590, #495) — thanks @mneves75, @tobiasbischoff.</li>
<li>Models/Auth: setup-token + token auth profiles; <code>clawdbot models auth order {get,set,clear}</code>; per-agent auth candidates in <code>/model status</code>; OAuth expiry checks in doctor/status.</li>
<li>Agent/System: claude-cli runner; <code>session_status</code> tool (and sandbox allow); adaptive context pruning default; system prompt messaging guidance + no auto self-update; eligible skills list injection; sub-agent context trimmed.</li>
<li>Commands: <code>/commands</code> list; <code>/models</code> alias; <code>/usage</code> alias; <code>/debug</code> runtime overrides + effective config view; <code>/config</code> chat updates + <code>/config get</code>; <code>config --section</code>.</li>
<li>CLI/Gateway: unified message tool + message subcommands; gateway discover (local + wide-area DNS-SD) with JSON/timeout; gateway status human-readable + JSON + SSH loopback; wide-area records include gatewayPort/sshPort/cliPath + tailnet DNS fallback.</li>
<li>CLI UX: logs output modes (pretty/plain/JSONL) + colorized health/daemon output; global <code>--no-color</code>; lobster palette in onboarding/config.</li>
<li>Dev ergonomics: gateway <code>--dev/--reset</code> + dev profile auto-config; C-3PO dev templates; dev gateway/TUI helper scripts.</li>
<li>Sandbox/Workspace: sandbox list/recreate commands; sync skills into sandbox workspace; sandbox browser auto-start.</li>
<li>Config/Onboarding: inline env vars; OpenAI API key flow to shared <code>~/.clawdbot/.env</code>; Opus 4.5 default prompt for Anthropic auth; QuickStart auto-install gateway (Node-only) + provider picker tweaks + skip-systemd flags; TUI bootstrap prompt (<code>tui --message</code>); remove Bun runtime choice.</li>
<li>Providers: Microsoft Teams provider (polling, attachments, outbound sends, requireMention, config reload/DM policy). (#404) — thanks @onutc</li>
<li>Providers: WhatsApp broadcast groups for multi-agent replies (#547) — thanks @pasogott; inbound media size cap configurable (#505) — thanks @koala73; identity-based message prefixes (#578) — thanks @p6l-richard.</li>
<li>Providers: Telegram inline keyboard buttons + callback payload routing (#491) — thanks @azade-c; cron topic delivery targets (#474/#478) — thanks @mitschabaude-bot, @nachoiacovino; <code>[[audio_as_voice]]</code> tag support (#490) — thanks @jarvis-medmatic.</li>
<li>Providers: Signal reactions + notifications with allowlist support.</li>
<li>Status/Usage: /status cost reporting + <code>/cost</code> lines; auth profile snippet; provider usage windows.</li>
<li>Control UI: mobile responsiveness (#558) — thanks @carlulsoe; queued messages + Enter-to-send (#527) — thanks @YuriNachos; session links (#471) — thanks @HazAT; reasoning view; skill install feedback (#445) — thanks @pkrmf; chat layout refresh (#475) — thanks @rahthakor; docs link + new session button; drop explicit <code>ui:install</code>.</li>
<li>TUI: agent picker + agents list RPC; improved status line.</li>
<li>Doctor/Daemon: audit/repair flows, permissions checks, supervisor config audits; provider status probes + warnings for Discord intents and Telegram privacy; last activity timestamps; gateway restart guidance.</li>
<li>Docs: Hetzner Docker VPS guide + cross-links (#556/#592) — thanks @Iamadig; Ansible guide (#545) — thanks @pasogott; provider troubleshooting index; hook parameter expansion (#532) — thanks @mcinteerj; model allowlist notes; OAuth deep dive; showcase refresh.</li>
<li>Apps/Branding: refreshed iOS/Android/macOS icons (#521) — thanks @fishfisher.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Fixes</h3>
<ul>
<li>Packaging: include MS Teams send module in npm tarball.</li>
<li>Sandbox/Browser: auto-start CDP endpoint; proxy CDP out of container for attachOnly; relax Bun fetch typing; align sandbox list output with config images.</li>
<li>Agents/Runtime: gate heartbeat prompt to default sessions; /stop aborts between tool calls; require explicit system-event session keys; guard small context windows; fix model fallback stringification; sessions_spawn inherits provider; failover on billing/credits; respect auth cooldown ordering; restore Anthropic OAuth tool dispatch + tool-name bypass; avoid OpenAI invalid reasoning replay; harden Gmail hook model defaults.</li>
<li>Agent history/schema: strip/skip empty assistant/error blocks to prevent session corruption/Claude 400s; scrub unsupported JSON Schema keywords + sanitize tool call IDs for Cloud Code Assist; simplify Gemini-compatible tool/session schemas; require raw for config.apply.</li>
<li>Auto-reply/Streaming: default audioAsVoice false; preserve audio_as_voice propagation + buffer audio blocks + guard voice notes; block reply ordering (timeout) + forced-block fence-safe; avoid chunk splits inside parentheses + fence-close breaks + invalid UTF-16 truncation; preserve inline directive spacing + allow whitespace in reply tags; filter NO_REPLY prefixes + normalize routed replies; suppress <think> leakage with separate Reasoning; block streaming defaults (off by default, minChars/idle tuning) + coalesced blocks; dedupe followup queue; restore explicit responsePrefix default.</li>
<li>Status/Commands: provider prefix in /status model display; usage filtering + provider mapping; auth label + usage snapshots (claude-cli fallback + optional claude.ai); show Verbose/Elevated only when enabled; compact usage/cost line + restore emoji-rich status; /status in directive-only + multi-directive handling; mention-bypass elevated handling; surface provider usage errors; wire /usage to /status; restore hidden gateway-daemon alias; fallback /model list when catalog unavailable.</li>
<li>WhatsApp: vCard/contact cards (prefer FN, include numbers, show all contacts, keep summary counts, better empty summaries); preserve group JIDs + normalize targets; resolve @lid mappings/JIDs (Baileys/auth-dir) + inbound mapping; route queued replies to sender; improve web listener errors + remove provider name from errors; record outbound activity account id; fix web media fetch errors; broadcast group history consistency.</li>
<li>Telegram: keep streamMode draft-only; long-poll conflict retries + update dedupe; grammY fetch mismatch fixes + restrict native fetch to Bun; suppress getUpdates stack traces; include user id in pairing; audio_as_voice handling fixes.</li>
<li>Discord/Slack: thread context helpers + forum thread starters; avoid category parent overrides; gateway reconnect logs + HELLO timeout + stop provider after reconnect exhaustion; DM recipient parsing for numeric IDs; remove incorrect limited warning; reply threading + mrkdwn edge cases; remove ack reactions after reply; gateway debug event visibility.</li>
<li>Signal: reaction handling safety; own-reaction matching (uuid+phone); UUID-only senders accepted; ignore reaction-only messages.</li>
<li>MS Teams: download image attachments reliably; fix top-level replies; stop on shutdown + honor chunk limits; normalize poll providers/deps; pairing label fixes.</li>
<li>iMessage: isolate group-ish threads by chat_id.</li>
<li>Gateway/Daemon/Doctor: atomic config writes; repair gateway service entrypoint + install switches; non-interactive legacy migrations; systemd unit alignment + KillMode=process; node bridge keepalive/pings; Launch at Login persistence; bundle ClawdbotKit resources + Swift 6.2 compat dylib; relay version check + remove smoke test; regen Swift GatewayModels + keep agent provider string; cron jobId alias + channel alias migration + main session key normalization; heartbeat Telegram accountId resolution; avoid WhatsApp fallback for internal runs; gateway listener error wording; serveBaseUrl param; honor gateway --dev; fix wide-area discovery updates; align agents.defaults schema; provider account metadata in daemon status; refresh Carbon patch for gateway fixes; restore doctor prompter initialValue handling.</li>
<li>Control UI/TUI: persist per-session verbose off + hide tool cards; logs tab opens at bottom; relative asset paths + landing cleanup; session labels lookup/persistence; stop pinning main session in recents; start logs at bottom; TUI status bar refresh + timeout handling + hide reasoning label when off.</li>
<li>Onboarding/Configure: QuickStart single-select provider picker; avoid Codex CLI false-expiry warnings; clarify WhatsApp owner prompt; fix Minimax hosted onboarding (agents.defaults + msteams heartbeat target); remove configure Control UI prompt; honor gateway --dev flag.</li>
</ul>
<h3>Maintenance</h3>
<ul>
<li>Dependencies: bump pi-* stack to 0.42.2.</li>
<li>Dependencies: Pi 0.40.0 bump (#543) — thanks @mcinteerj.</li>
<li>Build: Docker build cache layer (#605) — thanks @zknicker.</li>
</ul>
<p><a href="https://github.com/clawdbot/clawdbot/blob/main/CHANGELOG.md">View full changelog</a></p>
]]></description>
            <enclosure url="https://github.com/clawdbot/clawdbot/releases/download/v2026.1.9/Clawdbot-2026.1.9.zip" length="164165451" type="application/octet-stream" sparkle:edSignature="jlfk60gLuMIEOru5kFe7K7lLwsx1RBZGdUnkOR7FR3GAfLum7ocUb+QUO0ZtllUoGPEK0N1yc5BLB702LgLtAQ=="/>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>